http://www.breezetree.com/privacy

Toggle cookie consent banner
This site uses cookies to optimize functionality. Click Learn More to read our privacy policy.
Learn More
Accept
Privacy Policy
BreezeTree Software's Privacy Policy helps you understand how we collect and use the information that you provide us, and it helps you in making informed decisions when using this site and our software products.
If you install one of our software products, it will not gather, store, or transmit any personal information about you. The one exception is when you choose to use the "Check for Updates" feature in the product. This sends your product version number to the web site in order to determine whether there are any updates available.
BreezeTree collects two types of information: (1) personal information you knowingly choose to provide and (2) web site usage information. Each are covered below.
Personal information you choose to provide
Online Purchase
When you order online from BreezeTree, transactions are handled by a secure payment processing service. BreezeTree Software uses several ecommerce providers and links to their respective privacy policies appear on the purchase page. The payment processors do provide us with the customer's name, organization name, address (if applicable), and email address, but they not share credit card or other confidential financial information with BreezeTree.
Email
When you purchase a product, an cofirmation email will be sent to you providing you with a license key. A copy of the email is also sent to BreezeTree for record keeping. Also, if you send a support request or any other email to BreezeTree, BreezeTree may retain the content of the email messages together with your email address.
Web site usage information
Cookie usage
We use cookies for A/B testing different content on web pages. Our cookies do not track personally identifiable informaton.
Site Analytics
This site uses Google Analytics. It collects aggregate data on site visitor count and individual page views. It does not track information that would allow BreezeTree to personally identify visitors.
GDPR Compliance
We will delete any personally identifiable information upon request. Please note that because the only personally identifiable infomation that we retain is product order records, doing so would mean that we would not be able to confirm your eligibility for product support and upgrades.
Social Media Tracking
This website links to social media sites, but it uses non-tracking linking mechanisms (i.e., we do not embed their javascript in our site).
Sharing information with third parties
BreezeTree does not share or sell any personal information to 3rd parties. However, in the event that BreezeTree Software is ever acquired or merged with another company, BreezeTree retains the right to transfer customer purchase data (including name, organization name, email, address, license keys, and purchase date) as well as any recent web site visitor information, since these are common business assets transferred in such transactions.
